<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UnionApp</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>

    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="firstname">Firstname</string>
    <string name="surname">Surname</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="pwd">Password</string>
    <string name="pwd1">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="reg">Register</string>
    <string name="reg1">Register?</string>
    <string name="to_login">Already have an account?</string>


    <!--
        Draw item labels
    -->
    <string name="social">Social</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_1">Shop</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_2">Events</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_3">Societies</string>


    <string name="zones">Union Zones</string>
    <string name="union">Your Union</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_zone_1">Voice</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_zone_2">Activity</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_zone_3">Support</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_zone_4">Community</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>


    <string name="your_union_content">
        My name is Saskia and I am the President of the Students\' Union here at Surrey. As a Union we are here to represent your views as students and make sure your voice is heard, whether that be academic issues, accommodation, facilities – everything related to your experience here.



I started at Surrey in 2012 as an Undergraduate studying Dance and Culture BA (Hons), I then succesfully ran in the Surrey Decides elections in my final year to become VP Community, and again, earlier this year to become your 2017-18 Union President.



        My advice to all students at Surrey is to get involved with as much as you can: join that club or society, run to be a committee member, go on that trip, become a Course Rep or Community Rep, volunteer to be a Freshers Angel, get a part-time job, run in the student election. It\'s these opportunities that will enhance your time here, allow you to improve your skills and also inevitably increase your employability for when you leave. It\'s also through these activities that you will meet friends for life - trust me!

There are 5 full-time Sabbatical officers (a.k.a. Sabbs) elected each year and my team is made up of VP Support Jess Wreford, VP Voice Alex Harden, VP Activity Ali Douglass, and VP Community Helena Mason. As your Sabbs we feel passionately that all Surrey students should have the best university experience possible, and so each day we attend meetings and committees, we organise events and campaigns, we facilitate the running of sports clubs and societies – to make sure that the best experience is what you get. When you have a problem with the University that you can't resolve yourself, we are here to support you and help fight your corner.

Our offices are located in the SU building, below Rubix, please don't hesi​tate to come and see us if you ever have an issue - or just to say "Hi!".

You can also email me on ussu.president@surrey.ac.uk.

I hope you have a fantastic year here at Surrey, and I'm excited to be a part of it.​
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>
